Guide to the Broadway Tabernacle Church and Society Papers 1835-1980 (Bulk 1840-1970) MS 74
@ 2011 New-York Historical Society
Broadway Tabernacle Church and Society Papers
1835-1980 (bulk 1840-1970)
MS 74
@ 2011 New-York Historical Society
47.0 Linear feet
Containing materials dating from approximately 1835, this collection includes the organizational records of the Broadway Tabernacle Congregational Church starting in 1836 and traces the institution's evolution through 1980, focusing on the institution's internal machinations as well as its many community outreach programs that ranged from abolitionism to temperance to women's suffrage. A wide range of material is contained in the collection's 110 boxes, from Trustee meeting materials to architectural sketches to newspaper clippings to sermons.
Access Restrictions
Open to qualified researchers.
Photocopying undertaken by staff only. Limited to twenty exposures of stable, unbound material per day. (Researchers may not accrue unused copy amounts from previous days.) See guidelines in Reading Room for details.
Historical Note
Broadway Tabernacle, a Congregational Church created as a result of the religious upheaval of the 1830s, evolved into an important New York City religious center. Organized in 1836 with the financial help of reformers Lewis and Arthur Tappan as the Broadway Tabernacle Church, the institution boasted Charles Granderson Finney as its first pastor (he also played a key role in designing the building itself), albeit only for one year. After some internal organizational strife, abolitionist Joseph P. Thompson then assumed pastoral duties, guiding the church between 1845 and 1871. In addition to abolitionism (Church members raised funds to defend Africans captured aboard the Amistad and published an anti-slavery newspaper, the Independent), the Church advocated women's suffrage and temperance; not surprisingly, speakers at the Church included William Lloyd Garrison, Frederick Douglass, and Sojourner Truth. In this progressive vein, the Church granted women voting rights in 1871. Similarly, it sponsored mission activities globally, as well as educational and religious activities locally. Under the leadership of Charles Jefferson between 1897 and 1930, the Church provided weekly canteens for soldiers during World War I, provided a venue for local theatrical productions during the Great Depression, and once again provided weekly canteens to soldiers during the Second World War. For his part, Jefferson helped establish the New York Congregational Home for the Aged and the New York Peace Society. He later advocated for the League of Nations and the World Court. In 1928 the Church ordained a female minister; when Jefferson left two years later, Allan Knight Chalmers took over pastoral duties. A follower of the Social Gospel, Chalmers served as head of the national Scottsboro Defense Committee and as Treasurer of the NAACP. Finally, he, too, continued his predecessors' tradition of pacifism. Later in the twentieth century, the Church fought for global human rights and embraced the ecumenical movement epitomized by the Second Vatican Council. In fact, the Church became an Open and Affirming Congregation of the United Church of Christ in 1991, thus welcoming all worshippers regardless of their sexual orientation. Members supported Habitat for Humanity and ministered to prisoners, women on welfare, and persons with HIV and AIDS.
As New York City mushroomed in size and in population, Broadway Tabernacle coped with demographic shifts and economic challenges, at times even moving its congregation and selling its land. Ultimately, the Church changed its name and moved its physical location multiple times. More specifically, the Church's members worshipped until 1857 in the Broadway Tabernacle, located on Broadway between Worth Street and Catherine Lane, then beginning in 1859 from a new building at 6th Avenue and 34th Street, then from 1905 on in another new building on Broadway and 56th Street. Its name, meanwhile, changed from Broadway Tabernacle Church to Broadway Congregational Church in the early 1950s, then to Broadway United Church of Christ in 1957. Ultimately, the Church shared space with the Church of St. Paul the Apostle (Roman Catholic) starting in 1970, Rutgers Presbyterian Church starting in 1980, and St. Michael's Church (Episcopal) starting in 1985.
By and large, the Church's organization maintained a dual structure that included the Broadway Tabernacle Church and the Broadway Tabernacle Society. Whereas the Church focused on congregational and religious issues, the Society managed financial, real estate, and legal matters. The arrangement proved durable, lasting well over a century. But when the dual structure was dissolved, Broadway Tabernacle Church became the name used for all aspects of Church life and operation. In 1955, moreover, the name of the Church was changed to Broadway Congregational Church; finally, it became Broadway United Church of Christ, a name that remains in use currently.
Scope and Content Note
Containing materials dating from the mid-1830s, this collection includes the official records of the Church beginning in 1836 and traces the institution's evolution through 1980. Register headings and box labels alike reflect changes of name and of location over the 145 years covered by these materials. While the dual structure of the Broadway Tabernacle Church and the Broadway Tabernacle Society has been recognized, it is sometimes difficult to discern which papers belonged to which entity.
The collection includes 110 units: 103 boxes, two oversized folders, two tubes, two metal containers, and a large Bible. Materials include journals, publications, papers, photographs, newspapers, and architectural sketches. Meanwhile, materials from two Missions of Broadway Tabernacle Church retain their distinct status as Bethany Congregational Church and Martha Memorial Reformed Church.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged within the following ten series:
Series I. Journals, Annual Reports, and Printed Materials
Series II. Papers
Series III. Real Estate
Series IV. Committees and Programs of the Church
Series V. Bethany Congregational Church
Series VI. Martha Memorial Reformed Church
Series VII. Photographs
Series VIII. Architectural Sketches
Series IX. Blueprints and Offprints
Series X. Newspapers and Oversized Materials
American Home Missionary Society.; Broadway Tabernacle (New York, N.Y.) -- History.; Broadway Tabernacle (New York, N.Y.) -- Periodicals.; Broadway Tabernacle (New York, N.Y.). Women's Club; Broadway Tabernacle (New York, N.Y.); Broadway Tabernacle Anti-slavery Society.; Broadway Tabernacle Church (New York, N.Y.); Chalmers, Allan Knight, b. 1897; Finney, Charles Grandison, 1792-1875.; Hale, David, 1791-1849.; Jefferson, Charles Edward, 1860-1937.; New York Broadway Tabernacle Church (New York, N.Y.); New York State Anti-Slavery Society.; Stimson, Henry A. (Henry Albert), 1842-1936.; Tappan, Arthur, 1786-1865.; Tappan, Lewis, 1788-1873.; Taylor, William M. (William Mackergo), 1829-1895.; Thompson, Joseph Parrish, 1819-1879.; Antislavery movements -- United States.; Church buildings -- New York (State) -- New York -- Broadway Tabernacle.; Congregational churches -- New York (State) -- New York.; Home missions -- Societies, etc.; New York (N.Y.) -- Church history -- 19th century.; New York (N.Y.) -- Church history.; Slavery -- United States -- Controversial literature.; Slavery -- United States -- Societies, etc.; Temperance -- New York (State) -- New York.; United States -- Religion -- 19th century.
- Series I: Journals, Annual Reports, and Printed Materials
  Scope and Contents note
  - Subseries 1: Journals, 1840-1965
    This subseries includes 14 boxes.
    - Broadway Tabernacle Church Journal Book, 1840-1865 (Box 1)
    - Broadway Tabernacle Church Journal Book, 1865-1877 (Box 1)
    - Journal Record Book, 1840-1846 (Box 2)
    - Journal of Records of the Broadway Tabernacle Congregation from the date of organization, 20 October 1840 (Box 2)
    - Journal of Trustee Records of the Tabernacle Society, 1840-1848 (Box 2)
    - Journal of Minutes of the Meetings of the Board of Trustees of the Broadway Tabernacle Society, 2 November 1848 (Box 2)
    - Journal of Trustees of Broadway Tabernacle Society Records, number 3, 1857-1865 (Box 2)
    - Journal of Trustees of Broadway Tabernacle Society Records, number 4, 1865-1886 (Box 2)
    - Journal of Records of the Board of Trustees of Broadway Tabernacle Society, number 5, 1886-1905 (Box 3)
    - Journal of Records of the Board of Trustees of Broadway Tabernacle Society, number 6, 1905-1925 (Box 3)
    - Journal of Records of the Board of Trustees of Broadway Tabernacle Church, number 7, 1925-1942 (Box 3)
    - Journal of Records of the Board of Trustees of Broadway Tabernacle Society and Annual Corporate Meetings, number 8, 1943-1954 (Box 4)
    - Journal of Records of the Board of Trustees of Broadway Tabernacle Society and Annual Corporate Meetings, number 9, 1955-1960 (Box 4)
    - Journal of Records of the Board of Trustees of Broadway Tabernacle Society and Annual Corporate Meetings, number 10, 1961-1965 (Box 4)
    - Journal of Records of Committee, volume 1, 1843-1845 (Box 5)
    - Journal of Records of Committee, volume 2, 1846-1851 (Box 5)
    - Journal of Records of Committee, volume 3, 1851-1855 (Box 5)
    - Journal of Records of Committee, [volume 4], 1858-1864 (Box 5)
    - Journal of Records of the Committee of Broadway Tabernacle Church, volume 5, 1864-1871 (Box 6)
    - Journal of the Regular Committee Meetings, volume 6, 1871-1874 (Box 6)
    - Journal of the Regular Committee Meetings, volume 7, 1875-1877 (Box 6)
    - Journal of Records of the Committee Meetings, [volume 8], 1877-1886 (Box 6)
    - Journal of Records of the Committee Meetings, [volume 9], 1886-1894 (Box 6)
    - Journal of Records of the Committee Meetings, [volume 10], 1894-1901 (Box 6)
    - Journal of Records of the Committee Meetings, [volume 11], 1901-1905 (Box 7)
    - Journal of Records of Committee Meetings, [volume 12], 1905-1910 (Box 7)
    - Journal of Records of Committee Meetings, [volume 13], 1910-1912 (Box 7)
    - Journal Church Committees, 1912-1918 (Box 8)
    - Journal Church Committees, 1912-1920 (Box 8)
    - Journal of Church Committees, 1918-1929 (Box 9)
    - Journal of Church Committees, 1921-1943 (Box 10)
    - Journal of Church Committees, 1930-1951 (Box 11)
    - Journal of Church Committees, 1951-1962 (Box 12)
    - Journal of Records of Annual Corporate Meetings, 1944-1956 (Box 12)
    - Journal of Baptisms and Marriages, 1845-1848 (Box 13)
    - Journal of the Treasurer of the Broadway Tabernacle Society Accounts, 1849-1875 (Box 13)
    - Journal of Accounts of the Broadway Tabernacle Society, 1859-1865 (Box 13)
    - Journal of Broadway Tabernacle Society Building Fund, 1857-1858 (Box 13)
    - Ledger Book, 1842-1849 (Box 13)
    - Journal of Membership List and Addresses, undated (Box 14)
    - Journal of Burial and Funeral Records and Expenses, 1883-1893 (Box 14)
    - Journal of Church Membership Records, 1857-1878 (Box 14)
    - Journal of Church Membership Records, 1877-1892 (Box 14)
    - Hymnal, 1896 (Box 14)
    - Responsive Services, 1899 (Box 14)
  - Subseries 2: Annual Reports
    This subseries contains twelve boxes.
    - Annual Reports, numbers 1-6, 1842-1847 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Annual Reports, number 7, 1848 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Annual Reports, numbers 8-18, 1849-1859 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Annual Reports, numbers 19-27, 1860-1868 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Annual Reports, numbers 28-30, 1869-1871 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Annual Reports, numbers 31-33, 1872-1873 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Annual Reports, numbers 34-35, 1874-1875 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Annual Reports, numbers 36-37, 1877 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Annual Reports, number 38, 1878 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Annual Reports, 1841-1849 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Annual Reports, 1855-1857 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Annual Reports, 1880-1889, 1898 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Board of Trustee Reports, 1863-1879 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Annual Reports of the Trustees, 1900-1912 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Annual Report of the Trustees, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Annual Reports of the Church, 1872-1892 (Box 16)
    - Annual Reports of the Church, 1893-1903 (Box 17)
    - Annual Reports of the Church, 1904-1915 (Box 18)
    - Annual Reports of the Church, 1917-1926 (Box 19)
    - Annual Reports of the Church, 1927-1938 (Box 20)
    - Annual Reports of the Church, 1938-1945, 1947-1951 (Box 21)
    - Yearbook of the Broadway Tabernacle Church, 1952-1953 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Yearbook of the Broadway Tabernacle Church, 1954 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Broadway Tabernacle Church (Congregational), 1954 Annual Report of the Organizations (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Broadway Congregational Church Yearbook of the Church, 1955 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Broadway Congregational Church Yearbook of the Church, 1956 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Broadway Congregational Church Yearbook of the Church, 1957 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Broadway Congregational Church Yearbook of the Church, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Broadway Congregational Church Annual Report of the Organizations, 1955 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Broadway Congregational Church Annual Report of the Organizations, 1956 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Broadway Congregational Church Annual Report of the Organizations, 1957 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Broadway Congregational Church Annual Report of the Organizations, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Broadway Congregational Church Annual Reports of the Organizations, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Broadway Congregational Church Annual Reports of the Organizations, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Broadway Congregational Church Annual Reports of the Organizations, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Broadway United Church of Christ Annual Reports of the Organizations, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Broadway United Church of Christ Annual Reports of the Organizations, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Broadway United Church of Christ Annual Reports of the Organizations, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Broadway United Church of Christ Annual Reports of the Organizations, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Broadway United Church of Christ Annual Reports, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Broadway United Church of Christ Annual Reports, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Broadway United Church of Christ Annual Reports, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Broadway United Church of Christ Annual Reports, 1975-1976 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Broadway United Church of Christ Annual Reports, 1976-1977 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Broadway United Church of Christ Annual Reports, 1977-1978 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Broadway United Church of Christ Annual Reports, 1978-1979 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Church Psalmist, Broadway Tabernacle Church and Society, 1843 (Box 23)
    - Broadway Tabernacle Church, 1840-1880 (Box 23)
    - Annual Reports Broadway Tabernacle Church, 1872-1879 (Box 23)
    - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Year Book, 1872-1881 (Box 23)
    - Year Books, Broadway Tabernacle Church, 1880-1884 (Box 23)
    - Year Book, Broadway Tabernacle, 1881-1885 (Box 23)
    - Year Book, Broadway Tabernacle, 1886-1890 (Box 23)
    - Year Books, Broadway Tabernacle Church, 1885-1889 (Box 23)
    - Year Book of the Broadway Tabernacle Church, 1890 (Box 24)
    - Year Books, Broadway Tabernacle Church, 1890-1894 (Box 24)
    - Year Book, Broadway Tabernacle, 1891-1895 (Box 24)
    - Year Books, Broadway Tabernacle Church, 1895-1899 (Box 24)
    - Year Book, Broadway Tabernacle, 1896-1900 (Box 24)
    - Year Books, Broadway Tabernacle Church, 1900-1904 (Box 24)
    - Year Books, Broadway Tabernacle, 1905-1909 (Box 25)
    - Year Book, Broadway Tabernacle Church, 1900-1904 (Box 25)
    - Year Book, Broadway Tabernacle Church, 1905-1909 (Box 25)
    - Year Book, Broadway Tabernacle Church, 1910-1914 (Box 25)
    - Year Book, Broadway Tabernacle Church, 1915-1919 (Box 25)
    - Year Book, Broadway Tabernacle Church, 1920-1924 (Box 25)
    - Year Book, Broadway Tabernacle Church, 1925-1929 (Box 26)
    - Year Book, Broadway Tabernacle Church, 1930-1935 (Box 26)
    - Year Book, Broadway Tabernacle Church, 1936-1939 (Box 26)
  - Subseries 3: Printed Materials
    This subseries contains seventeen boxes and contains numerous sermons, reports, manuals, guides, and minutes, as well as historical materials pertaining to the Church.
    - Henry Ward Beecher, "Manual of the Plymouth Church, Brooklyn, N.Y.", 1854 (Box 27)
    - Newell Dwi, "Henry Ward Beecher: A Sermon Preached in Plymouth Church", 1903 (Box 27)
    - "Thirtieth Annual Report of the New-York City Tract Society, Auxiliary to the American Tract Society, with the Thirty-Fourth Annual Report of the Female Branch, December 21, 1856" (Box 27)
    - "Twenty-Third Annual Report of the American Female Guardian Society and Home for the Friendless", 1857 (Box 27)
    - "Thirty-First Report of the American Home Missionary Society, May 13, 1857" (Box 27)
    - J.M. Sturtevant, "A Discourse in Behalf of the American Home Missionary Society", 1857 (Box 27)
    - "Forty-First Annual Report of the New York Sunday School Union, May 1857" (Box 27)
    - The American Missionary, 1857 (Box 27)
    - "Thirty-Second Annual Report of the American Tract Society, Presented at New York, May 13, 1857" (Box 27)
    - "Fourth Annual Report of the Children's Aid Society, February, 1857" (Box 27)
    - "Thirty-Sixth Annual Report...of the Clinton Hall Association", 1857 (Box 27)
    - "Thirty-Third Annual Report of the New York Bible Society, November 1856", 1857 (Box 27)
    - "Guide for 1857-1858" (Box 27)
    - M.L.P. Thompson, "Annual Sermon Before the American Board of Commissioners for Foreign Missions", 1857 (Box 28)
    - "Forty-Eighth Report of the American Board of Commissioners for Foreign Missions", 1857 (Box 28)
    - "Thirty-Third Annual Report of the American Sunday School Union; Presented at the Annual Meeting, May 12, 1857" (Box 28)
    - "Forty-First Annual Report of the American Bible Society, Presented May 14, 1857" (Box 28)
    - The New Englander, 1857 (Box 28)
    - "Reports of the Secretary and Treasurer of the Central Committee...for Disbursing the Fifty Thousand Dollar Building Fund", 1856 (Box 28)
    - "Twenty-Eighth Annual Report of the Congregational Board of Publication", 1857 (Box 28)
    - "American Congregational Year-Book, for the Year 1857" (Box 28)
    - "Minutes of the General Association of New York, for 1863" (Box 28)
    - "Minutes of the General Association of New York, for 1864" (Box 28)
    - Joseph P. Thompson, "The Faithful Preacher. A Discourse Commemorative of the Late Dirck C. Lansing", 1857 (Box 29)
    - Joseph P. Thompson, "The Last Sabbath in the Broadway Tabernacle: A Historical Discourse", 1857 (Box 29)
    - William M. Taylor, "Broadway Tabernacle Church: Its History and Work", 1871 (Box 29)
    - William M. Taylor, "Sermon Before the American Board of Commissioners for Foreign Missions", 1876 (Box 29)
    - William M. Taylor, "At the End of Twenty Years", 1892 (Box 29)
    - Charles E. Jefferson, "The Broadway Tabernacle of the Past and Future", 1901 (Box 29)
    - Charles E. Jefferson, "Congregationalism: Its Origin, Principles and Mission. A Sermon", 1901 (Box 29)
    - Charles E. Jefferson, "Address at the Memorial Service in Honor of Our Lamented President William McKinley", 1901 (Box 29)
    - Charles E. Jefferson, "The Broadway Tabernacle of the Twentieth Century. Endowment Funds", [1902] (Box 29)
    - Charles E. Jefferson, "Congregationalism: Its Contribution to Education", 1902 (Box 29)
    - Charles E. Jefferson, "Why Join the Church?", undated (Box 29)
    - Charles E. Jefferson, "Broadway Tabernacle", 1905 (Box 29)
    - Charles E. Jefferson, "The Knighthood Needed Now", undated (Box 29)
    - William M. Taylor, "Tenth Anniversary Sermon", 1908 (Box 29)
    - William M. Taylor, "Original Year", 1910 (Box 29)
    - "Pilgrim Hall: Its Needs and Uses", 1914 (Box 29)
    - William M. Taylor, "The Cause of the War", [1915] (Box 29)
    - William M. Taylor, "Sermon to the Boys and Girls of Broadway Tabernacle", 1920 (Box 29)
    - William M. Taylor, "The Appeal of the Christian Ministry", 1922 (Box 29)
    - William M. Taylor, "Twenty-Fifth Anniversary Sermon", 1923 (Box 29)
    - William M. Taylor, "Thirtieth Anniversary Sermon", 1928 (Box 29)
    - William M. Taylor, "Varieties of Pacifism", [1929] (Box 29)
    - William M. Taylor, "The Next Step", [1929] (Box 29)
    - William M. Taylor, "Thirty Years on Broadway", [1929] (Box 29)
    - William M. Taylor, "At the End of Thirty-Two Years. A Sermon", 1930 (Box 29)
    - Allan Knight Chalmers, "The Tabernacle: A Spirit and a Building. An Historical Sermon", 1935 (Box 29)
    - Allan Knight Chalmers, "This is My Country", 1935 (Box 29)
    - "Over One Hundred Years on Broadway: A Sketch of the History, Program and Facilities of the Broadway Tabernacle Church", [1950] (Box 29)
    - "A Financial History of the Broadway Tabernacle", [1950] (Box 29)
    - Albert J. Penner, "The Day of Resurrection", 1952 (Box 29)
    - Albert J. Penner, "Where to Find Life's Meaning", 1950 (Box 29)
    - Albert J. Penner, "Linking Life with Life", 1950 (Box 29)
    - Albert J. Penner, "Whence Comes Peace of Mind?", 1950 (Box 29)
    - Albert J. Penner, "Find Yourself Through Faith", 1950 (Box 29)
    - "Broadway Congregational Church (United Church of Christ)", undated (Box 29)
    - "Proposed Constitution and By-Laws of the United Church of Christ and Second Report of the Commission to Prepare a Constitution", 1960 (Box 29)
    - Frank J. Scribner, "The Needle's Eye", 1961 (Box 29)
    - "Relief Goes as Straight as an Arrow", undated (Box 29)
    - "History of BTC with the Articles of Faith and Covenant, and Complete Catalogues of the Members of the Church", 1846 (Box 30)
    - "Manual of the Broadway Tabernacle Church", 1855 (Box 30)
    - "Constitution and By-Laws af the Pitts Association, Broadway Tabernacle, New York", 1859 (Box 30)
    - "Manual of the BTC", 1860 (Box 30)
    - "Manual of the BTC", 1866 (Box 30)
    - "Manual of the BTC", 1869 (Box 30)
    - "Supplement to Catalogue of the Officers and Members of the BTC", 1869 (Box 30)
    - "Manual of the BTC", 1873 (Box 30)
    - "Hymns for Tabernacle Worship", undated (Box 30)
    - "Churches: A Tour of Places of Worship in New York City", undated (Box 30)
    - "Young People's Society of Christian Endeavor", 1913 (Box 30)
    - "What the Broadway Tabernacle Likes to See in its Members", undated (Box 30)
    - "Constitution and By-Laws, BTC", 1947 (Box 30)
    - "Constitution and By-Laws, Broadway United Church of Christ", 1966 (Box 30)
    - "Over 100 Years on Broadway, A Sketch of the History, Program and FAcilities of the Broadway Congregational Church", undated (Box 30)
    - "Minutes of the New York General Association, for 1870", 1871 (Box 31)
    - "In Memorium: Mary E. Willard", 1882 (Box 31)
    - "The Congregational Year-Book, 1902" (Box 31)
    - "Addresses at the One Hundredth Anniversary of the Dedication of the House of Worship of the United Church, New Haven, Connecticut, 1916" (Box 31)
    - "Missions in India and Ceylon", 1917 (Box 31)
    - "Present-Day Opportunities for Christian Life Service in America and Abroad", [1921] (Box 31)
    - George Warren Hinman, "The Orientals in America", undated (Box 31)
    - "Survey of the Missionary and Educational Work of the Congregational Churches in all the World, 1920-1921, issued by the Commission of the National Council on the Congregational World Movement" (Box 31)
    - George Warren Hinman, "Our Caribbean Neighbors", [1930] (Box 31)
    - "Men and the Church", [1935] (Box 31)
    - "Reports of the Congregational Pension Boards", 1937 (Box 31)